I got a little beat of the show I don't know I don't know what her deal is
Hi, how are you? How's your morning? I'm okay. I just woke up. Well, I got a bagel and some coffee, so I'm just waking up still though
You have your coffee. You might not be fully awake. It's true. Well, how's your night last night?
You have a good night?
It wasn't particularly good because you know
Is it just me or is these YouTube streets becoming more drama drama drama is like so much if I could hardly take it
But did you watch last night what happened? Oh, yeah, I watched a little bit and then I got
Then I said fuck it. I just decided to troll at that point. I was like fuck it
Okay, well, you know, I was like half asleep. What are you? What are you specifically talking about you want to say it or?
I went on to beat us
Oh, yeah, those they're being bullies in there. By the way, they're emotional as fuck. I don't know why they're emotional for
Yeah, I mean, it's like I should I shouldn't have and what was the whole thing?
Let me ask you what was the whole thing about her not her but that girl saying that like
Like summer like a doctor or something. I even fucking know
Saying that summer said that summer was docs and then she said Christine didn't
Care or do anything about it and then Christina saying well, she's done so much for summer and
It's not reciprocated or something like that. I don't want to get in the middle of
Yeah, I mean either
That's their relationship. I did bring it up because I know because the reason I think I heard that
Um, Christine was trying to convince some are like not to not to deal with me anymore because of
Do you know a girl? Do you know girl it starts with a C? Can I say it on your panel?
Um, or Christine
You know, no, it starts when we see it. Um, it's like a
They go like oh, yeah like a crystal. Okay
Yeah, do you know here?
Do I know her? Yeah, I know her she fucking hates my guts because in the only reason she can say is because I
Hang out on your panel. That's literally the only reason why she hates me, right?
I mean, it's like oh, yeah, then goes to the bait or saying hi to you. I know I mean, it's like
Well, I don't know that is but um, yeah, I mean she um
You know he's a troll or it might be a woman. I don't fucking know who that is. Yeah
I'm doing it. Hey, by the way, shout out to you, brother. You trolling early as fuck, dog. Shout out to you
Me?
No, shout out to Ghost of the Beta. You trolling early, brother.
Okay, that's the beta.
Props from the real Ghost. Okay. There you go. Well, like, I don't know, like...
There's only, listen, sir. There's only one Ghost.
There's so, I mean, it was just so, so cruel to me, like, you know, it's like...
I still understand
So here's my tactic and let me let me give you a little like let me inside information
Maybe go to the bait or he'll clip it and put on his channel
But here's the thing they're like yeah, I can debate him
But if they're too dumb to have the debate, I just trolled him
Well, I don't think those two debaters gonna come up to debate with you
I think that you know the troll in the background by the fact he should be blocked
But I'm not that kind of person that would ask that of you, but he is using my picture what she didn't have permission
Okay
Nobody can really even see it. I mean it's like I won't put it up on the screen am I making a big deal out of it
I don't give a fuck what you do
Okay, no, you're not I just I was like I'm gonna be mindful of like, you know
Try not to dox people like you know, but uh
Let's see so okay, so they say let's run one ghost. Okay, come on up
He's just using my cats
Ghosts, you know, they're not gonna come up. They're just saying they're saying they're they're baking. I don't know
One room with the real ghosts are you too scared who's afraid of ghosts we can run one
I know I'm well, they're welcome up here, but they're not I don't see anybody in the backstage though
Because these are trollies shouldn't be up here. We should block
Matter of fact, actually if you don't come up here, we're gonna block you
And that's on and that's on
and that's on and that's on
Well, but did you see Mason last night Mason did a good job on what no, I did not see that
Well, I said I said Mason go over to beat us and then I ended and guess you went over to beat us
Anyone it's not even being a good job. You just got to troll those people because they're emotional
They don't know what the fuck they're talking about
Here's my problem. I sometimes I take them serious and that's my whole problem. You can't take these people serious
I know, but I mean it's like I try to like talk to people with logic and like empathy and, you know, and I try to...
Kind of me, but it's like yeah, we're always degenerates. It always gets into like
You said the problem what you said logic, but your second word was empathy
See that was that's where you fucked up the empathy word
Well, empathy is good to have because that's like I mean understanding
Oh, you really do you think it worked out this far to have empathy for these people? You know what they do do you?
Empathy and sympathy is two different things. Empathy is feeling sad for someone. Empathy is putting your shoes like it felt like you do what they do
I could never do what they do. Have I ever doxed?
When I'm saying though empathy is putting your putting like wearing their shoes. Have I ever P-bombed? Have I ever doxed ever?
I don't have the empathy for them. Fuck them
And I don't really
You know what I do have sympathy for him sympathy meaning like I feel sad for him
Yeah, I feel sad that they're too stupid to have a conversation and it's really sad that there some people are like that though
So I don't want to like beat up on them
But then sometimes they sound intelligent, but then you didn't after you talked to him for about two minutes
It's like oh this person
The fact that they're breathing is a miracle the fact they didn't know how to breathe
You're a pristine
Huh?
You're a pristine like you know
for asking me and stuff.
I even gave her credit.
I was like, yeah, you defended me once,
but then she'd like went off on a whole tin.
And this is why I ever got mad at me.
Everyone loves Christine,
but I called her out for that whole armchair.
I called her out like four times I called her out
and improved it with facts.
Everyone beat me up for it.
I mean, yeah.
I mean, it's like, you know, she'll go, oh, oh, oh.
And then she like, you know,
everything's like red herring too.
It's always like, oh, well, I like it.
Oh, psyche with the fallacies.
Let's go.
I like it.
I understand logical fallacies because I deal with so many of them in some of these conversations that I've learned, you know, all these, like, little tactics and tricks people use to...
No, I guarantee you any any of these YouTube sheets. No one knows no one debates
Listen, everyone's trolling. They're either let me make my statement and everyone clip it because I'll be real right now
I'll be real as I can ever be ever on YouTube either
They're trolling or they're just too dumb to have a conversation. Let me ask with you
Well, yeah, but here's the thing I get beat up because like oh you beat up on like a dumb person
I didn't know they were dumb. I thought they were trolling
I knew and who brought up that name like someone can bring up the name of that of that person like you know that
I don't want to bring it up, but it's like
Well, there's a couple people. It's either
There's like three people that me RG Goddy, and there's another person that does it
Why does Goddy bring it up?
I mean, I mean, I mean, I mean,
Yeah, oh, I love it. Yeah, just by with the chat goes probably the chat. I'm watching
No, I'm chatting with you. I just want to get under the covers a little bit. I was under the covers last night
They're like we can't hear you on your microphone. I'm like, I'm gonna know the covers. They're like, oh, you
pathetic
Are you fighting with your chat?
Well, I'm talking I mean if there's lurking was them right now, you know, is they they're gonna get they're afraid that you know
They're afraid they're gonna call some kind of name by beta or you know, Christine
You think you care Christine calls you a name
No, I don't even care what name it is. I wouldn't care. It's just words
They're terrible name, so no, no, you know what I retract my statement
Yeah, because if she is she coming like a PDF file. Yeah, I'd care
Yeah, well, so she was doing basically by saying you know, it is what she is she did she was too stupid to understand
I was like she wasn't calling me. Well here. I'll make her argument. I'm not calling you a PDF file goes
But you're a PD you're a PDF file sympathizer sympathizer like dude. That's a
Like that's basically almost I know it's not the same thing, but it's fucking close
First of all is invoking the invoking the word. It's like using that
That brings it up to it
She'd even make the fucking argument that I was she was saying that you were and I support you and you support him
Therefore I support him. What the fuck kind of argument is that trying to say that anybody that comes to my chat is that right?
It's like in a roundabout way, which is like do they do that to good times good times has the same person in his chest
Yeah, but we can't understand good times. He talks a drunk ish. He has his own language
Well, I mean, I'm, I'm, I'm telling you, I'm drunk. I'm, I'm stonedish right now. Who else? And then, oh,
Oh, he's speaking a stoned language, brother. Stoned inch.
I'm kind of like, you know, exterminate all creditors. Then it's like, he has like,
Oh, that's, that's not him. That's fucking clumsy.
I know I'm that's another person I'm saying there's good time if they both have that this person on their show or in their chat
And then nobody goes up to them. No, it's a bunch of dum-dums making up some dum-dum topics
Yeah, if you want to exterminate operators. Yeah, I agree with that, but you just a dumb dummy making up dumb ass things
right and then I
Mean it's like
It's really silly.
By the way, I've been on comsies panel and I'm sure everyone can clip it.
I mean, he might be here listening.
I don't know.
I've been on his panel and I destroyed everyone up there.
They don't know what the fuck they're talking about.
Well, yeah, I see him like doing drugs and like long asleep on his panel.
So you ever see that?
We can think.
You know
By the way, that dude's like a major simp any woman that comes up there. He always like fucking kisses her ass
Have you ever did you notice that?
But then you let Jamie get attacked you know Jamie did so much for him. Oh, he went against his own code
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's her good attack and called
By the way, Jamie is not smart, but she's definitely smarter than that dude. Oh, yeah
I mean, it's not hard to be smarter than him
I mean, you know how the twangle goes into the triangle say you put it in the twangle or not the rectangle
Okay, yeah, I know he's a little but he's a little bit
Samans in boxers in his bed and like looking at the covers are showing his boxers to Sam and like all all morning
Did Sam man like it? Yeah
He's like, oh my god. He's so excited
Oh my god. Oh my god
He's like and then he's like, oh, you know keep your up. Keep your hands above the above the covers
Because his hands could go under like I said the guy that gets the last views and he's he's also stupid
But at least he lets me up there. It's fucking LES. At least he lets me up there at least we can fucking talk about shit
Right. Well, he was another one targeted kind of by the Christine thing, you know
And uh, Christine is targeting everyone now. She's a victim. She thinks she's uh, she thinks she's like a
Well, if you're on youtube for so long, you talk so much stupid shit and people call you out. You're gonna get targeted
Yeah, she thinks it makes a major player now, so
You can cry we can come defend you, but if what they're saying is true
It's true, but if they're saying if they're lying about you, I'll defend your ass. I mean you defend me. I'll defend her, you know
Wait, I mean I think the past month has been the victim olympics
Yeah, everyone's victim now. Well, I'm not trying to be I'm gonna say I just
like you know
treated like a
corpse or like
And an object to be to be used and weaponized on it. I mean say I'm not like
Not you see what I did though
You know that dude that was in the chat that try to be like ghostly debater
You see when you'd like if you don't attention or always needs attention when you don't give them attention look what happened
They left
Yeah, they got that scared because they didn't want to debate with the real
I don't want to run run, but you don't give them attention. I'll give you attention. All right, come up here
I want some attention
Tell me I'm beautiful
You ugly as fuck. Oh
Wait, what I'm also black. You kind of look like that thing from Ghostbusters. That's why they call me ghost
You look like you look like you
look like Slammer and the
marshmallow man. Did you just
call me a team version of
over rain? No, I said you're
slacker. No, that's not that
marshmallow man melded
together. You look like the
Michelin man. Don't play with
me. I because I just use that
on you. You said marshmallow
man. I said Michelin man. He's
based on that. Well, it's two
Marshmallow Vans a little bit cooler. Yeah, your head looks like that moon. You look like the Death Star. Don't play with me
Keep playing with me. My head's under the blanket. You can't even see me
Well, I've seen it enough. Trust me. Why does it smell like syrup under it? No, but hey Paul
It's not like pancakes in my under my blanket. That's so good
When we get under here with me
Hey, yo
I'm talking to your cap. Oh
Yeah, yeah the cap
You talking a little no over
Yeah
Have you watched spider-man nor? Oh, she she she's not a big Toby McGuire fan
That's Nicholas Cage brother. I'm talking about spider-man nor air. She a Nicholas Cage fan. She hates Nicholas Cage
Fuck that cat live
Hey, she's about to have eight lives. She keep talking like that. Yeah, you're about to have, you know, eight seven lives
She's gonna take one with you
Do you want to get spanked? I can do it you're over here. I was gonna say did you post a link?
Yeah, the link's there
Yeah, he posted again like and I taught people from the chat to get them to join
There's nobody in the chat. How many people are nobody in the chat? Yeah, there's nobody in there
No, no, there's some vegan. Yeah eat some broccoli. There's some vegan
Just be in patriot
Yeah, they called you Charles Manson. You're gonna take that from them. I
Am I'm Charles Manson. I'm a little bit better looking, but yeah
With co-leaders
with great musicians
Both of them too much acid
Pretty much almost the same person
little less but I have a little I have a
Much less people much less, you know bodies in my past. I don't have any bodies in my past
So for yours. I want to taste your body, honey, honey. I thought you were giving card readings.
I'm just, I'm channeling it to blankets. What do you want to know?
Nancy!
How are you doing, Shadi?
How are you, Nancy?
Now, shh, Nancy, how are you doing, yeah, huh?
How are you doing?
All fancy life.
Excuse me, miss. I saw me from across the room
Sit on it. Oh bounce on that motherfucker. Yeah, my bad. Oh, yeah
Are you doing a little shawty little Nancy? How you doing? Yeah?
Now hit the link where the fuck is Jamie at least she hits the link
Well, you're breathing in the mic. You're breathing in my ear. I got headphones on
I don't even know how to say your name but not top top top 9777. How you doing shawty?
It's like, it's like, there ain't no way you just passed out that quick.
What the fuck is going on?
Apollo, I don't fucking know, Doc.
So like, there's no way you just passed out instantly like that.
You were literally just talking.
There ain't no way this motherfucker just fell asleep that quick.
Nah, you're trolling. Stop trolling, Doc.
I'm awake, kinda.
Well, motherfucker, you just, you tripped everybody in the chat.
Everyone's like, is he sleeping?
There's no way you fell asleep that quick.
I'm like, I'm like, I'm actually like, I smoke, I look for pot and I get so sleepy with it.
Yeah, but you don't fall asleep that fuck. You don't fall asleep instantly. You just had a full
conversation. I mean, a full sentence and I have coffee too, but I'm waiting for Paul.
Do you know who Paul is? Paul, oh yeah, like he's a, he's a Greek guy.
He's a Greek guy.
He's in the chat. Well, he was in the back. He wanted to join, I thought.
That's when you were going
There is I got him I got him
Greetings
Were you freaking out to you this motherfucker? We're just having a sentence literally a second later you went
I don't maybe strong or someone who knows I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm trying to listen. I'm gonna start to do my bagel and drink more coffee, okay?
That's a contradiction there man
Long time no talk there goes
I haven't talked to you for a while brother. How you doing? How you been? Well, I'm doing perfect
The fight which fight are you see fights down the way it's at White House. Oh
No, I don't I don't watch this bullshit. This is all fixed and shit. No, no, I watch the
Football World Cup, you know
Yeah, soccer soccer, yes
Yeah, when you say football, I always think like, you know, like, you know, I know I have to switch my mind to things like an American, you know, do you do like miles or do you do metrics metrics?
No, Mike, he's a devil. Get him out of here. It's like, you get him out.
No, by the way, you've got that care on and you look like you're loving that egg
Oh, you look like you're loving that dog. Oh, it's very good
Did you see last night I went on to beat us and my Christine confronted me and
Oh, the usual the usual
Where are you? You should have been up there. That'd have been fun
No, it's not what my time there. Trust me. I had my my I had my fun with Christine and some
I think that you just don't like the drama. Is that fair? No. Oh, you like the drama
No, I don't. Oh, yeah. Well, that's what I was saying. Yeah. Yeah, that's well, you know
Did you ever hear me talking about someone private life? Never. Did you ever hear me?
I'll vouch for Apollo right now. I've never heard him say that
See, did you ever hear ever hear me cursing at someone called someone bitch or ho or whatever?
No
never
Well, you call me a ho once
That's a bit somebody else, but you know what they you know, Christine starts bringing up my family and
And and you know, and then they say they start saying oh, well, where's where's my cat, you know, they ran away
Apollo said that's like Apollo just said that you you are a nappy asshole. That's what I heard
Come on I told Mason I was like Mason go over there and see what's up
And so Mason came over and then they're like, oh my god
I don't think Mason is your best warrior to send over there
Well, he got it. Let's just say let's just say he was successful
But they're like, well, what do you want and they were so rude to him and Mason was just like he's like what's going on
I'm gonna be rude to Mason
Me just like I'll come back some other time. He's left
What makes you say can Mason Mason ever says anything?
Can't really say much. He was like show his picture
J1 J1 never says anything, but he just asked questions
And Jay was never argued with anyone. He only all he does is like, well, let me ask you this and he'll ask a question
He's like, okay, let me ask this
Yeah, one was on beat as any said. Oh, be the um
Why don't when you get a porn bomb you just write a letter to YouTube and they'll know that you know
It wasn't you that put it up there and then you won't get in trouble and you don't delete your episode or stop
That was his logic. That was gonna put it and then that Boston that horrible Boston bridge. It was like a motherfucker
Why are you talking to me in the chat? Well, you're so weird and he's like shut up, lady
Then she and then you know, he like sick of sick of suck up for himself
Because if you don't like it leave, oh, okay. Yeah, it was crazy, but yeah
I think
There's been so much drama on these cheap shoots. That's why I think that is back off
I just saw it, I didn't see it.
You remember me? Oh, she's saying hi in the chat.
Yeah.
This is my brother Apollo for 50 cents a day. You can feed him.
But never feed me after night, okay, never feed me after night, you know what's happening.
If you feed them at night, it's like a hydra.
You cut one head off, they grown it too.
All of a sudden we got like fucking 16 napalos running around.
Yeah, that's the gremlin's ghost.
Exactly.
That's why I like the size.
You should tell it.
You get it right away.
It's a great you keep talking I'm a third water and you don't play with me
No, please
There's a funny key and peel skit. It's like you ever see gremlins 2 or hear of gremlins 2
Yeah, so yeah, I'll play this on this this is a really short key and peel
About gremlins, too. It's really funny. I'll play real quick. I don't know if you probably haven't seen this one
I don't know why you're making fun of a Pablo's family like that
This is called so this is called the gremlins brainstorm
Hold on. Let me just get it up. Okay. Okay, so I got it. I got it. Watch this real quick. It's the short, so just a three-minute
Hilarious skit about Gremlins 2. I think you'll love it. Here, watch this.
No, I have to piss anyway.
Hey, watch this, Paula. Paula, watch this.
Okay.
Okay, guys.
Gremlins 2.
I'm telling you, this movie should bite itself.
So this is, I guess this is supposed to be Steven Spielberg, I'm not sure exactly, but let me see it. Okay, so here we go
Okay guys gremlins 2
I'm telling you, this movie should write itself.
The first one was a classic.
This should be pretty straightforward.
Basically, all we're doing is maintaining
the integrity of the original picture.
We want to do all the stuff with the water and the...
Can we help you?
I'm sorry.
Let me introduce myself. Hi y'all. My name is Star Magic Jackson Jr.
I'm the Hollywood sequel doctor, so studio just brings me in to oversee things when they're about to drop a deuce.
So that's why I'm here, but don't mind me. I'm just gonna be over here. Y'all do your thing. It's your movie.
Okay. Damn, that looks like Bristos.
Adam if it's gonna take place in an office building
I was thinking what if gizmo gets wet from a water glue this time. Okay, hold on a second
I'm sorry. I'm all right to step in here. Just one second. So what's wrong with y'all?
Y'all looking like a bunch of sad sacks. This is
G2 people we're writing gremlins too. It should be a party with pizza and anchovies pineapple
Just come on, lift up the spirits.
Look, okay, I'm gonna put a little bit of spice
into the mixture here.
What if we did this?
Everybody here gets to design their own gremlin.
Um, I don't see that the, uh, the Gremlin design is broken.
It's called Brainstorm, and I'm Braindrizzlin' Sweet Pea.
Okay? Shut your mouth for a second.
Look, here's the thing.
None of this is finals.
So you mean, like, what if there was, like, a brainy Gremlin?
No.
a brain and gremlin.
You talking about a gremlin with glasses
who could talk and sing New York, New York?
That's brilliant.
It's in the movie done.
Hey, double.
Whoa, whoa, you said that nothing was final.
That was before I heard the words
brain and gremlin in the same sentence together.
It's done, I love it.
It's in the movie next.
What about a spider gremlin he's gremlin with eight legs and a thorax just catching pretty ladies in a web and an office building
Oh my god, it's in the movie. I love it
What about a bat gremlin you mean a gremlin with leathery wings just flying around flip-flop and bust through a wall make a perfect bat
Single in the wall get outside getting some wet concrete jump up on a building that just dry in place like a gargoyle gremlin
We are cooking with gas now. I love it. It's in the movie
Could there be a female gremlin if stick boobies bitch you have me and little gremlin, but JJ
I love it so much that it's not only in the movie, but it's definitely in the movie
There's no backsies on now or no penny taxis. Yes. Yes. Yes in the movie dog
That's why we need a woman in the writer's room next. I don't know
Gugli I'd probably
But you do know, because you talk about a gremlin who sold purpose in this film, it's just that he looks stupid as fuck, yes.
It can be in the movie and it is in the movie done next.
What about you, Silver Pie?
Of electricity grandma, you just say noun and gremlin.
Like you're playing Madeline, you're just like a child.
You have the brain of a child.
You do not have a high IQ, but you have habits.
And you came up with a gremlin that's
just made out of bolts that is zigzagging all over the room
and is done completely in animation.
You a crazy person.
And your idea's in the hope that you're done.
Next.
Can we put the Hulkster in it?
What?
You talking about putting Hulk Hulking,
turned actor, turned cultural icon in the movie
where he break the fourth wall of the movie.
He's in by talking to the audience.
You sir, I'm a raging psychopath.
I don't even care anymore.
We got the Hulkster in this bitch, so it's done.
I don't have any more time.
So let me just recap right now.
It's Brainy Gremlin, Spider Gremlin,
Back Gremlin, Lady Gremlin,
Gugliak Gremlin, Electricity Gremlin,
Hulk Hogan's gonna be in the picture.
I'm gonna throw in a Gremlin myself.
Vegetable gremlin just write it up. I'm having so much fun. Thank you
It's all gonna be in the actual film now. I got to go put some cowboys and back to the future three
Sayonara y'all
No, okay, you guys know that none of that is gonna be in the actual movie
Can I give my comment first? Yes, go ahead
That shit was so gay remind me of Apollo and bubbles. Oh my god
Well, what happened was the way some are saying she's gonna strike me what what what I do
Don't do anything
You know why you know why she's also auto control she can't control their emotions
I didn't say her name I always said was I talked to Christine who was like, you know bad mouthing her stuff
Don't understand why anyone takes the summer serious seriously. She has only for a few sentences suck my dick your mother has
There is some I say it to anyone like my dick your mother should have swear swallow it
That's the only thing she can say. She's so limited
She's so limited in a in a conversation seriously. She only has five sentences. She can say that's all
Yeah
there's a few minutes ago like what's going on i don't understand we can join forces and stuff
i don't know i don't know i i i wanted you to test something you know and i joined it uh
someone else's uh i test it i joined someone else's partner and direct 20 seconds after after
i joined it summer summer joined it kicker terry you know she paid a lot of dollars to pick terry
I don't care about and I left I left I let us stay like a dumb idiot
She took the bait
Remember I did the same with Christine the first time I joined this panel. I did the same
But then he just left anyway
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
I'll be okay. I don't think I don't know what the fuck he's talking about. I'll be straight up with you
I think I think it's a victim. I think whoa a little dumb
I also think he doesn't know what he's talking about. I also think he doesn't have no social skills
I'm talking about you you pussy. I said Apollo as your name
Oh, I was thinking you're talking about yourself
I know you are, but what am I? What kind of argument is that? What are you in fifth grade?
Shut the fuck up when I'm talking, by the way. So you sound stupid.
Uh-huh.
And what I was saying was, you don't know what the fuck I'm talking about.
Yes.
Don't bring Summer's name up, because you don't know what to talk about.
What era democrantum?
I don't have to defend that, bitch.
That's what the states your Americans have
English as a first language and you repeat the same five sentences over and over
And that's why you marry your fucking that's why you marry 13 years. I mean we all have our own crosses the bear
I mean, yeah, we repeat the same sentence you marry kids. I mean we all have our own crosses there, right?
What goes
Yeah, exactly
Shut the fuck up inward shut the fuck up inward. That's all they can do
And word my Caucasian don't do that
This is not going really well cuz he's a little stupid. I'll be honest with you. This is a little he's open to
There's Nancy and someone else's pendant
She took the bait, you know, do you understand the fucking thing? I'll be honest with you
It is what it is.
I don't think it is what I want.
I understood that one.
It is what it is.
Yeah.
Don't come up here talking shit about other panels trying to get drama started.
We're not interested in it.
We're up here hanging out.
We don't care about other panels.
You come here and mention.
Okay.
People's names.
Shut the fuck up.
We don't care about it.
Okay.
So that's going to be a good rule.
Shut the fuck up.
Okay.
Okay, sure. I'm with us. You're acting like his mother goes
I'm not his mother. I'm his daddy
I shut the fuck up
Fucking speak English if you're gonna come up here and talk some shit
Nobody gives a fuck what summer did you you got your ass foot by summer ain't our fault we didn't do it to you fuck off
I'm gonna crash the fuck out. Are you pissing me off? Oh, please please do
I'm gonna crash out. You're being all but hurt like a little fucking pussy. Oh summer did this and summer did that
Nobody gets a fuck. It's not summer's panel up here dumb-ass. It's like a panel. I don't give a fuck what you think
By the way, you probably deserved that shit to be honest with you
You smell like a pussy, you act like a pussy, you crack like a pussy, you smell like a pussy, you smell like a pussy, you might just be a fucking pussy!
I want to say the R word but like you won't let me say that but if you sound like a dumb dumb you might be a dumb dumb
Now listen, that's the fucking second ball. Don't come up here and mention another fucking YouTube creator's name
This is like this thing
Unless you're gonna pay some money then we'll then we'll say their names
Okay, so if you just if you're too stupid to have a conversation you probably shouldn't have it fourth of all
Conversation, okay, let's let's start the conversation
Start the conversation want you every time I come up here some are there some are there some are there some of that
I don't give a fuck. She whooped your ass in a debate and now you're all brokered about it
Yeah, right
You're fucking cooking you're seizing
You're yapping
You're breaking all the fallacies. You're beating a dead horse. Nobody you got your ass whooped. It's okay
It's like if you got knocked out of the boxer, you're gonna keep talking about it. Yeah, you gotta knock out
You might find it again. That's true. But you got knocked out. That's the truth of it. Move on.
Pussy. And that was about like a two out of ten crash up, but you keep pushing it. Keep pushing it.
Everyone see yesterday's clip?
Got knocked out. Move it on.
Showing Sam in is everywhere.
Come on, fuck it. Can I give it an eight out of ten? Fuck it.
Did you see Clumsy showing Sam?
The man yesterday kept showing his underwear to Sam.
He's fucking pussy. I don't see any place where people are gonna kiss my ass.
Hey
No, we're talking about I asked another question I forgot I forgot what I asked
His underwear yesterday and like laying in bed like doing sexy you bring up some gay shit
Well, yeah
And he said, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we, what do we
Oh my god, I think stay gay stay gay
Yes
He's very feminine. He was raised by a single mother. I'm surprised he's not in prison or something
But if you're not in prison, you become gay
Did he hit on you to see who was like ghost butt?
Yeah, same, same guy told you he hit on me though, he's like I'll say I said no, no, no.
I don't fuck around with that shit, y'all.
Yeah, but this is the reason why I'm friends with you, and you're the reason why.
He was like, he thought I was gay because I hang out with you.
Yeah, maybe.
Yeah.
You bring me nothing but troubles man. I got to get in debates the finger ass or I get beat up every night because I'm friends with you
Also, they think I'm gay because I
Friend is a hard thing to do side. Oh, and I like it
All it doesn't care
What Paul is fucking stupid. I mean he's like dog. Oh, you can't get right. It's like how do you thought about this?
And he's in the corner drawing
No, because what the fuck he thinks sorry, Paul
No, it's okay.
Hey, this motherfucker's rolling the corner.
Somebody did this, somebody did that, somebody did that.
Nobody gives a fuck what somebody did.
Get you up here with us.
And tell me what summer did and I guarantee you summer didn't do that to you because I actually know summer a little bit
I'm not saying I'm her friend or nothing, but I know her a little bit
I know she's more logical than you. I know she can argue more than you
She's definitely smarter than you and that bitch is no
What she is
You took me
I don't know. The fact that you're breathing is like a year. You're a miracle. You're a miracle.
Harry could fuck her husband. She upset her over and over again.
Yeah, like well, it's like destiny. They're cucks. Summer's a cuck and their husband's a cuck.
They like they're like to be cuckold.
They're not cuck. Summer likes to use a strap on.
Oh, you don't have to ask her. I wouldn't be surprised.
She doesn't need a bowler. I know that.
Hey, you're been pegged, ghost.
That means everyone I told you to stop asking me dumbass questions. Oh, it's good, but that was a good question though
That was how is that a good question? Please explain. I'm picturing it and laughing
Oh, I'm feeling a crash out your ass is pushing you better leave me the fuck alone. Don't ask me dumbass questions, dog
Okay, but have you ever been pegged?
Strike you want to go to stick to you? I've got my soul set up
Well, fuck I asked me five of them pegs. That's not bad me getting that question, dog
That was gay every he ever made love to a man you'll want to
But a woman does it to you
Don't force your sexual army. Okay, but a woman does it so how is it gay?
You're receiving it. I can't be gay. I don't know if it's necessarily fucking homosexuality with a woman
But no, don't ask me dumb ass questions. No, I don't do that shit
I don't even lick pussy. I'm a fucking man. I don't bow down to a woman to lick pussy. You got me fucked up. I'm a man
You got me fucked up. It's gay to lick pussy. You think I'm gonna let her fuck me? You got me fucked up. I ain't even lick pussy
I'm a man, dawg
Yeah, we fucked up gay that you don't you don't eat the data. How's it get only I don't eat pussy. I was like gay
I look like a vampire sir
I'm superior to her in every way
Maybe if that bitch is low enough after years I might bat on to give her a ring one time in my life
I ain't bound on the woman
I'll push you to shut up before I punch Apollo in his face.
Hey.
Oh my God.
Well.
We've already been caught.
No, fuck this.
Let me ask Apollo.
You ever been tagged?
You saw where that question is?
Apollo, have you ever had, have you ever licked a vagina?
No comments.
A vagina doesn't mean you still do it.
What the fuck?
Ghost says he doesn't do that.
I ain't bound down to a woman. I'd never right there's there's so
So I'm so much better than them. I'll never bow down to would you bow down to a superior man?
Never let's say what my ass and even then unless they kill me. I'll fucking kill her up and fight him again
So basically
Hey listen stop asking me dumbass question stop asking gay ex question. Was that fair?
No, I'm gonna get on your ass
No, and I know you'd like that because you think about that homo shit, but I mean get on your ass
I'm gonna get on you for real. Stop playing with me. You're gonna get on my ass. Oh, sounds kinky
I knew he was gonna make a gay follow. I knew he was gonna make that gay
We're the one who said it. I mean you said it. I did walk myself into that. I wouldn't miss that. I didn't walk myself into that trap
I didn't walk myself into it
Oh, I'm getting heartburn from the
Yeah, why are you so, why are you breathing like that, are you excited?
To get on your nerves.
You're not getting on my nerves, you can never get on my nerves. Come on now.
You see me, hold on.
I can't see you, it looks like you're like Harry Potter with a cloak of invisibility.
Now I'm Moana.
You kind of look dumb too.
You look like a dumb lumberjack.
Sorry.
father or something. How far I'll go. Oh, ghosty. How, when I get in bed with you, it
so feels so toasty. Oh, damn. And like a palo. Whenever it's in me. It's, it's getting
halting here. Oh, okay. Let's take off all your clothes. It's getting all your clothes.
But Paolo, what do you think, like,
because I had somebody on my show now,
not only are they calling me Predator Projector,
but anybody that comes to my chat,
like they call it ghost tech.
They're calling me, I'm catching strays.
Ghost doesn't even know the person,
or I've never talked to them.
Yeah, I don't even know who the fuck that is.
It's like, but they're calling it,
but it's like the person goes to other shows,
and it's like, yeah.
Yeah, Paolo, what do you think about that?
You see, like, it's just me, just me,
and they're saying, just like, boycott me, and I'm bad.
even though i'm not even talk to the person anymore it's like i'm still i'm still that word they're saying you know
well i'll tell you i'll just i'll just like sprain and i get smoked
the thing is it's not uh trust me i don't know what happens but i don't need to know it's the same
script over and over they did the same shit to multiple payments the same script the same nothing
Listen, guys, they're trash talking TPP, okay, but in my opinion, a panel is not the owner, it's the people who join the panel.
and then they turn a TPP to a bully, a doxy and trash dog panel, pure.
They did it, not the owner, not the owner.
It was awesome, Apollo was awesome in the first half.
And then after they can't control TPP anymore,
they start a trash dog being named, calling, reporting,
trying to take it down.
and all this shit and they do the same shit to you now, they're doing the same shit to
L.S.
I can tell you, I can give you at last 10 panels where the Samaritans did the same shit
and it's always played innocent, always, they did nothing wrong, never.
But that's why that's why I don't join penance or anymore, you know, because these people I don't know what my time
Yeah
Discussion they all talk about discussion that all are here is shut the fuck up fuck your mom fuck your mom
That's my dick suck my dick. That's all they've been talking about. That's a discussion
Trust me, mark my word, mark my word, next it's bitter spandex, bitter spandex is going to go down by some mind Christine. Mark my word, I predicted it for multiple panels and I was always right.
I mean, tell that last part I agree with everything you just said.
Oh.
I don't think it's summer in Christine, but I this is
So drama they don't know how to have a like a like a fucking argument. They don't know how to do it
Try to make a person all day as a hominin they're trying to attack you as a person to study your argument
But how many you're attacking the person not the argument and I agree with everything you just said
I don't think it's something like I've seen maybe and maybe I was looking through a little bit more
Maybe I've changed my mind, but everything you just said I agree with besides that last part
Yeah, I agree with you too. They all talking about discussion and shit. Nah, on the other panel, you know,
I say it for Nancy. On the other panel, I join it and the first thing someone did, the picture of my eye.
Like, I care. She has so much advantage to me because she has a picture of my eye.
That's how eager she is to hurt someone, to make fun of someone.
She has so much anger and hate inside her, it's going to be sweet.
Yeah, I feel like, Apollo, would you agree if it's like, oh, I'm not the one bullying
you, but I'll lie on my channel?
Is that what they're doing?
Are you at the center?
They used my picture too, and I was like, I don't like that.
Can you take it down, suck this bitch?
Exactly, and then you use your phone.
But here's it, Derek says, I'm not bullying you,
but I'll let other people do it.
Yeah, they have minions. They have stupid minions that they don't do it by themselves. Trust me
Well, if the summer auto Christine do is doing something by themselves that dump minions, you know, like like a tree now
Like money like the gay bird they have all these male or low IQ New Yorker idiots will we do that the dirty work of them?
Yeah
No like you New York. Yeah
All this dump in a low IQ is a low surface in New York
I don't want to build an argument this there's nothing to win or to lose nothing
At that point. No, there's nothing to win. I like there's nothing I even if you win it. What are you really winning nothing?
It's all in the in the head of someone. It's all in the head
You just prove that they're low IQ then if you join them again
Then you feel bad for debating them because you know, they're low IQ. So it's like you're beat me
You're beating a dead horse, you know
Like you do, right? I try not to I try not I start a troll
I know what you try but they try to we were involved anyone in drama anyone
Today they love you, tomorrow in two weeks they hate you, and then in another two weeks they hate you again.
No, no, no, no, no, not two weeks, one day they hate you, one day they hate you.
Okay, okay. It's completely worthless, whatever the...
Hey listen, if you kiss them, they're like women, they're like women.
I don't care if they are women, I don't care.
Exactly. Let me talk to you right now. Let me talk to you. Let me talk all this shit, which I don't even get involved with these YouTube dumbasses.
Trust me. If I have the time and the, let's say, the time and the work, I'm willing to do it as they say what they did in the past.
To other people to me. Oh my god. Anyone would see that Christine and then some are the cancer of any panel
Any panel
No, no talking about no talking about kids. No talking about kids. Oh my god, seriously
It's like Jeffrey Dahmer say don't don't kill people
Man, you're a serial killer
Oh, there's other bitches that like that Jeffrey Dahmer
You ever see that Apollo sorry, but there's a lot of bitches that loved Jeffrey Dahmer and believe it or not
You ever see that? No
I don't I don't know something seriously wrong with the woman on this planet something seriously wrong
They are either sexually frustrated or all mentally ill
Well Katrina, you know, there's a link would you like me to post again? You can join
you know Katrina is one of them you know trust me she's just a minion she's doing the dirty work
she's just doing the she called her Kevin Kevin yeah the minion
number one minute Kevin yeah we should call her Kevin now okay
But listen bitch the link's there. You want to join join don't touch it in the comments
Doesn't that make me so frustrated when people like to touch it in the comments. We don't want to see their picture
They come it's okay. You know what?
It's a free world anyone can do what you have whatever he likes. It's a free world
It's a free world. I could like some that's seen I could argue against that
It's a free word. I could murder people
That's for your world, right?
If Katrina don't want to respect you, you have dignity.
I just don't understand.
How can you lower yourself that much
and be just a slave for someone crazy, like Summer?
A slave, literally a slave and do the dirty work.
I don't want to make arguments.
I could, but maybe it's maybe you and her thing.
I don't want to make her argument.
Imagine how low and self-esteem you must have.
I mean, you can debate, but I don't want to debate about Summer.
I mean, have the conversation with her, brother.
I'm sure she's willing to.
Huh?
Can you speak English?
We're talking about Summer.
I don't feel like I should talk about her.
I'm sure she's willing to have the conversation with her.
Was she the one that made those things or whatever you're talking about?
She never had any conversation with anyone.
You just up here to fucking trauma dump about summer. I don't give a fuck. I don't care. Okay. I'm sure nobody here cares
Okay
Okay, I'm always with the best way. I don't give a fuck
Is that fair? So you want to have a discussion a debate? I'm not gonna about what?
I'm not gonna argue about summer if you want to promise you you want some smoke with her or show accepted
I guarantee show accepted
Mm-hmm
Okay, cool. You got a problem with me or do you want to just hang out or are you trying to be?
Oh my God, you are so boring, man. Seriously.
No, you came up here with a picture about summer. We don't give a fuck!
Who is we?
I mean, honestly, we don't give a fuck about none of that.
Uh-huh.
Are you paying or not? Okay, anything else?
Or you just came up here with a drama. Do you even have a theater drama done?
Okay, we're not a therapist either. We don't give a fuck.
Mm-hmm. Yeah, we you want to keep drama dumping? I won't let me say I don't give a fuck
Drama jumping trauma dumping, I don't give a fuck summer did this summer did that it's not summer's panel pussy join her panel
Sure
He did that's the only reason you can't appear if you fucking do that
Yes, yes
You want to talk about it?
No, I don't want to I'm not summer dumbass. What would I want to talk about it?
So I look like summer do I talk like summer do I act like summer?
What the fuck? I don't think talk to her about it
Kyla a dumb dumb. What do you say?
Don't breathe in my ear like that either. I got headphones on me breathing way too heavy
Second of all, I need oxygen
Nobody gives a fuck about the issue. We don't care. We literally don't care
The game we yeah, we it's like a collective. I'm not putting you in it. I'm not putting like yeah
I'm just like saying we like you know like a lot of people. Oh
That's like
If I say if I say most if I say all you're gonna make argument about it the world works on generalities
so if i say like women want this usually it works like most women that could be 51% to 99%
i negative you don't understand the follow you never did understand it but i'm telling you right
now just to use that where the fuck does it grab on my ear you fucking weirdo the fuck are you
bringing my ear like that stop doing that shit
If you've got a problem with summer, why are you up here? You've got a problem with summer go on summer channel
Wait, did she walk your ass? No, you're not allowed back up there. Yeah, right? What's happening? I'm just asking questions
Answer it yourself
You got you bitch. I'm alone on every panel. What kind of man that one?
Never got my ass kicked them all out another channel
What the fuck do you mean?
You're the one that, you know, you're breathing all heavy because she's not here to defend herself,
but you like to talk about her shit.
I'm not gonna let you talk shit about her.
She's not here to defend herself.
Shut the fuck up.
Let's hang out.
Don't talk shit about someone that's not here.
Shut the fuck up.
Yeah?
Because if she, well, here's the thing though.
If she was here to defend herself, you'd get your ass kicked.
And that's in a real way.
You know you would, pussy.
Fuck you.
Yeah, summer's here. She fucked you up. There's not what happened summer fucked you up last time and that's why you're so
But I heard about it. Hey, you lost the debate move on. She doesn't keep her feelings. You got you fucked up move on
It's a debate brother just move on literally if you're mad that night. Okay, the next day move on
Why do you keep in the grudge for you got fucked up? No, do I have to do I have to be the reason or do I have to be the reason
I like the voice of reason
Sir, you got, you got defeated in the debate, it doesn't mean no one doesn't like you, it doesn't mean everyone hates you, it doesn't mean we don't, like you can't hang out, dude you got defeated, I've been defeated, we've all got our asses in the debate, move on, stop holding the grudge, what are you holding the grudge about by the way, what's your biggest problem with her, fuck it, we finna run by now, Apollo, now we finna get us in a debate, what's your biggest problem with her, cause she, I'll debate at you, I'm going to get to you.
All I'm saying is don't talk shit about people that aren't here.
I wouldn't let them do it about psyche, I've never let them, I'm not gonna let you do it about someone.
If you don't know what the fuck you're talking about, shut the fuck up or let her defend herself, but...
I thought you were smirking that Apollo.
Apollo, are you still here?
Well, don't leave because I called you out in your shit.
Yeah, 420, I know you're in the chat, start your panel, dog.
Apollo's been a bitch if you got called out.
Wait, guys, did I just kick Apollo's ass that easy?
Haha, liptoed pushback.
Haha, he didn't realize what the fuck he was talking about.
Hey, shut the fuck up.
Hahahahaha
Well, let's do the chat.
That's how you kick someone's ass.
You just call them out for their bullshit.
They don't know what the fuck they're talking about.
Is everybody here or something?
Okay.
I'm gonna make a bed.
You may.
I'll be back later.